Ankita apurba pattanaik

in www.linkedin.com/in/ankita-apurba-pattanaik-272373210

PROFILE

Junior Full-Stack-Web Developer specializing in front end development and Backend development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, Dotnet - having Ado.net and Asp.net library knowledge, OOP concept, JavaScript, CSS,SQL Server, Angular 13 and React. Strong background in Supply chain Mangement and customer relations,e-com projects, payment gateway integration.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend developer

02/2023 - present

At 56N software pvt ltd

I am working on the technologies like html, css, bootstrap, angular, javascript, react

.

Creating web application projects for the use of customers and according to the client requirements.

Have used and Hands On Experience in using - GitHub, Gitlab and git.

Full stack web developer

07/2022 - 12/2022

At Cozentus

I am working on the technologies like dotnet, sql server and html, css, bootstrap, angular, node.js and react.

Have used external libraries like - ado.net , node.js ,ssms, jquery , react.js Creating web application projects for the use of customers using the above mentioned technologies.

Have used and Hands On Experience in using - GitHub, Azure Vm And Gitlab

Intern 01/2022 - 07/2022

At Cozentus

I am working on the technologies like dotnet, sql server and html, css, bootstrap, angular, node.js, react and have been trained in particular technologies. Have used external libraries like - ado.net, ssms, jquery. Have used and Hands On Experience in using - GitHub, Azure Vm And Gitlab

EDUCATION

MCA 07/2020 - 07/2022

Institute of technical education and research

Secured Scgpa - 8.5 scgpa

Graduation 07/2017 - 07/2020

Utkal University

Secured Scgpa - 8.0 scgpa

07/2015 - 06/2017

Christ College

Secured percentile - 53.66%.

SKILLS

- Angular
- SQL
- Dotnet (Ado.net, asp.net) And C#
- html,css
- Javascript
- pl/sql
- Figma
- Node.Js
- React

LANGUAGES

Hindi, Odia, English

• • • •

PROJECTS

Asset Management system

03/2022 - 05/2022

worked in technology - html,css,bootstrap,angular, node.js, mongo db.

ServiceDesk 06/2022 - 09/2022

Ticket management Tool

It was a ticket management tool through which ticket is created through the user and can be asigned by HR department . Worked in the technology -

 $html, css, bootstrap, angular, popper js, dotnet using ado.net \ library, sql \ server, \ Firebase \ (Google \ cloud) \ .$

Byb Application 10/2022 – 12/2022

Bring Your Buddies

A hiring application for the experience freshers and candidates registration applicationand job posting for every job for the candidates. Worked in the technologies-html,css,bootstrap,react, javascript, jquery, dotnet using ado.net library and sql server

Payment Gateway Integration 05/2021 - 09/2021

worked with the technologies using - html, reactjs, css, node.js, javascript and mysql

CERTIFICATES

Java Certification completed Python Web Development

Level 1 Level 1 level 1

ACHEIVEMENTS

Got Best Academic Project Award From My College. Got selected for college president.

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that above mentioned informations are true

Ankita apurba pattanaik